echemi.com 2016-09-12

# Make Chemical Transaction Easier_Echemi.com

Welcome to visit ECHEMI.COM! We promise to protect visitors privacy by this Privacy Policy. The following words is published the situation of using & collecting information by us (Echemi.com).  Our Privacy Policy is updating whenever necessary. We welcome you look over this policy at any time, and response your valuable comments to info@echemi.com

When you accept Terms of Use by Echemi, you already accepted us to use and disclosure personal data according to this Privacy Policy. The whole Terms of this Privacy Policy are part of Terms of Use.

MINORS

The Sites and their contents are not targeted to minors (those under the age of 18) and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors, so we wish you don’t provide any personal data to us if you are under 18 year’s old. Minors could only use our service with parental or guardian consent.

SECURITY MEASURES

For registered users of the Sites, your Registration Information and Account Information (if any) can be viewed and edited through your account, which is protected by a password.

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access to the Sites, to maintain data accuracy and to ensure the correct use of the information we hold.

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. You could only use your password to use your account. You may face some problem if you disclosure your personal, so we kindly ask you to make the account and password safely. If any reason related to your password safety, please contact us as soon as possible via info@echemi.com

REGISTRATION INFORMATION

We ask you to fill out the Registration Form while you want to join us. It is asked to provide your real name, address, country, telephone number, email etc. Beside, it is also asked to provide your company name& address, telephone number, your company service & product in short words, etc. You also has the right to choose to fill in additional information. We will use these statistics to give our members classification, such as industries, products, so that targeted to provide new services to our members and opportunities. We'll let you know by your email address to the new services and opportunities.

YOUR TRANSACTION BEHAVIOR

We record and retain records of users' buying and browsing activities on our platform including but not limited to IP addresses, browsing patterns and buyer behavioral patterns. In addition, we gather statistical information about the Sites and visitors to the Sites including, but not limited to, IP addresses, browser software, operating system, software and hardware attributes, pages viewed, number of sessions and unique visitors (together "Browsing Information").

In Order to provide our Members with recommended products and service, we would classify our Members by statistics data which is brought from the transactions. We would inform you these new products and chances by email.

AUTOMATIC DATA COLLECTION

It’s potentially to received and record data from your browser and computer automatically by Echemi, which is including your IP Address, cookie information, software & hardware character, and the web records for your needs.

ABOUT COOKIES

Cookies is a few of datas, it would be sent to your browser and stored in your computer's hardware if you don't refuse to accept it. We use cookies to store the related datas which you visited our website, when you visit our website, it helps us to recoganize your indentity and provide you better and more services accorrding to analysis datas.

You have the right to choose accpeting or rejecting cookies. You could reject cookies by modifying your browser settings, but we kindly remind that, you may not be able to use parts of functions on our website because of reject cookies.

PUBLISH & USE OF INFORMATION

We would not provide, sell, rent, share or trade our Members’ Personal Information. Anyhow, for the convenience of your use of Echemi services and services from the companies/organizations related to Echemi (short for other services), you agree and authorize Echemi to transfer your personal information both to you and other services parties, or agree Echemi to get your personal information from other services parties.

We will make a comprehensive statistics for your(company's) identity and transaction data, and might provide to some advertiser which with reasonable purchase and usage by Echemi judgement. But under this situation, we would not pulish any information which might be recoganize members' personal indentity, but not limited to the members' user name or other information disclosed.

You agree that we may publish or use your personal information to identify and (or) confirm your identity, resolve disputes, make sure the security of website, help ensure that the site is secure, restrict fraud, illegal or other criminal activities,in order to enforce our service agreements.

You agree that we may use your personal information to protect your life, property, or to prevent serious damage to the legitimate rights and interests of others or the need for public interest.

You agree that we may use your personal information to improve our services and more fit for your requirement. It would bring you better use services from us.

Our website has announced the business opportunities and offers, while users can check these offers and business opportunities.

When we are forced by law or government or the right people to identify the alleged violations of the people's request to provide your information, we will be in good faith to disclose your information.

STORAGE AND EXCHANGE OF INFORMATION

The collected user information and data will be stored in the Echemi and / or its Server.

EXTERNAL LINK

Our site is including other links. Echemi is not reponsible for he privacy of those links. We may increase the quantities of our business partners or shared brand’s websites at any time.

SAFETY

Our website have the appropriate security measures to ensure that the our data is not lost, misused and altered. These security measures include the backup data to other servers and the user password encryption. Although we have these security measures, please note that there is no "perfect security measures" on the Internet "

MODIFY YOUR DATA

You can modify or update your personal information and password in "MY ORDERS" on www.echemi.com

CONTACT US

If you have any comments and suggestions on this privacy policy or Echemi privacy protection measures as well as your questions while use our website, please contact us: info@echemi.com

**Changes of the content shall not give you further notice.**

**Final interpretation power of this Privacy Policy is belong to ECHEMI.COM**
